<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/changes/1.0.0"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/changes/1.0.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/changes-1.0.0.xsd">
	<properties>
		<title>PRE</title>
		<author email="kedar.raybagkar@mastek.com">Kedar Raybagkar</author>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<release version="30.2.2.0" date="2014-09-24" description="Fixes and Enhancements">
			<action dev="kedarr" type="add">
				Provided mechanism to propagate the status change of the request to the
				interested listeners. Listeners need to register themselves to listen
				to status change updates
			</action>
			<action dev="kedarr" type="fix">
				Changes made to work in cluster using the CLUSTER_MAP.
				Due to use of 2 different map names at 2 different location the clustering
				was failing. Fixed the issue. 
			</action>
		</release>
		<release version="30.2.1.0" date="2014-07-10" description="Fixes and Enhancements">
			<action dev="kedarr" type="fix">
				SimpleDateFormat being used as class variable introduced in 30.2.0.0 resulted into concurrency issue as
				the class is not thread safe. Fixed the concurrency issue. 
			</action>
			<action dev="kedarr" type="add">
				getParams() method signature has been changed from HashMap to Map. Also it now returns an unmodifiable map.
			</action>
		</release>
		<release version="30.2.0.0" date="2013-07-30" description="Enhancements">
			<action dev="kedarr" date="06/26/2013" type="add">
				Removed licensing requirement completely from PRE.
  		</action>
			<action dev="kedarr" date="8/23/2012" type="add">
				Two new API in form of interfaces exposed namely Singleton and Service.	New plug-in framework is created by these
				interfaces as any startup programs can now be associated with the property startUpClasses defined in pr.properties.
				The values can be in the following format key:className;key:className etc. where key is the id by which the class
				instance can be accessed through the PREContext. A new method is provided in the PREContext to retrieve the singleton
				class. Only those classes that implement Singleton are made accessible through the PREContext. It is not mandatory to
				add key and if left blank the fully qualified className will be considered as the key.

				The plug-in project is created separately.

				The BIRT integration that was part and parcel of PRE earlier has now been externalized and will not be part of PRE. For this
				you will have to get hold of the birt plugin project and its deliverables.
  		</action>
		</release>
		<release version="30.0.x" description="Refer to change log.">
			<action>
				Refer to the ChangeLog.html for all previous releases.
  		</action>
		</release>
	</body>
</document>